ticketnest.com 2007-06-16

# Policies : Ticket Nest

TicketNest is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program.  TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to build user’s trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices.  Because this Web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact Ron Arthur at [art@sofizar.com](mailto:art@sofizar.com). If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily address, you should contact TRUSTe at http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns.

_ _ TicketNest.com is firmly committed to protecting your privacy while you are visiting our Web site. The following Privacy Policy discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for [www.TicketLuck.com](http://www.ticketluck.com/). ****  

**INFORMATION THIS SITE GATHERS/TRACKS**   
We use your IP address and browser type to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. This means that a user's session will be tracked, but the user will remain anonymous. This means that your session is never associated with any of your personal information.   
The Contact Us form has the following mandatory fields:

  1. Name: This is used to address the person, seeking to contact us.
  2. E-Mail: This is used to respond to the person, seeking to contact us.
  3. Verification Code: This is an auto generated number to prevent automated programs such as web robots to spam us.
  4. Query: This is the body of the text.

The contact form also has the following optional fields which are used to facilitate communication, should the person feel it’s necessary. These fields are:  
Address, Telephone & Fax and Company name.  
All mandatory fields are denoted with an asterisk(*).  
**CORRECTING/UPDATING INFORMATION**  
We never store any information after responding to your email and therefore it is not possible for you to update the information. If your contact information has changed, you will have to resubmit the contact information.  
**_Security_**  
We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it.  No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however.  Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.   
**_Changes to this privacy policy_**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our homepage.

**  “Purchasing tickets”-**  
When purchasing tickets we direct you to our third party ticket provider's site to complete the purchase process.  You are providing your personal information such as name address, and credit card number to that third party directly.   In some cases the pages may be framed so it appears you are still on our web site to provide you a seamless purchase process.   In these cases you are actually on our third party ticket provider's  web site and your information is being collected by that site.   
The information collected on these sites is governed by their privacy policies and we encourage you to read their posted privacy policy.

**  Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)**   
We use Third Party Service Providers to assist us in analyzing the aggregate information about the visitors on our site. This information, which helps us optimize the usability of our site, is collected via Service Provider cookie or log files. We do not link any aggregate information to PII.   
**Cookies**   
We use cookies to keep track of your shopping cart, customize your future shopping, and to assist your needs. These are java script based first party cookies and are unable to link to personally identifiable information (PII). Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies on our site.  We have no access to or control over these cookies. 

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by this site only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.   
**LINKS**   
This site contains links to other sites. This site is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. We encourage you to read posted privacy statements whenever interacting with any Web site. We will not share any specific information that you provide to us without your explicit permission to share it. We may share broad demographic information with others. We will never release your personal information (including but not limited to your name, email address, street address, and phone number) without your express permission.   
_Customer Service Emails_ ****  
Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us we will communicate with you in response to your inquiries or to provide the services you request. We will communicate with you by email or telephone, in accordance with your wishes. If you do not wish to receive emails from us please do not submit any.  
**CONTACT US**   
If you have any questions about this privacy policy or the security practices of this site, please contact us through on of the methods listed on the contact us page of each site   

<http://www.ticketnest.com/contact.php>  
<http://www.ixs.net/contact.aspx>  
<http://www.ticketnest.net/contact.php>

Or   
Customer Care at [sara@ticketnest.com](mailto:sara@ticketluck.com), or by contacting us by postal mail at the contact information listed below. ****  
Sofizar Inc.  
4010 Crescent Point,  
Carlsbad, CA 92008 

## _Legal Disclaimer_

_We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site_
